
export const cardData=[
    {
        question:"9 + 6 + 7x - 2x - 3",
        answer:"Ans = 5x + 12"
    } ,
    {
        question:"8 + 5 + 6x - 3x - 4",
        answer:"Ans =  9 + 3x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"10 + 7 + 8x - 3x - 2",
        answer:"Ans =  15 + 5x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"12 + 4 + 9x - 1x - 5",
        answer:"Ans =  11 + 8x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"11 + 3 + 5x - 4x - 1",
        answer:"Ans = x + 13"
    } , 
    {
        question:"7 + 9 + 4x - 2x - 6",
        answer:"Ans = 2x + 10"
    } , 
    {
        question:"13 + 2 + 3x - 5x - 7",
        answer:"8 - 2x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"6 + 8 + 2x - 6x - 8",
        answer:"6 - 4x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"14 + 1 + x - 7x - 9",
        answer:"6 - 6x"
    } , 
    {
        question:"15 + 10 + 11x - 8x - 10",
        answer:"3x + 15"
    } ,  
]